[
    
    Get Ready to Roar! Dinosaurs come alive these school holidays at the Jurassic Zoo.
    
    Find out more](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/jurassiczoo)
    
    [Book Your Visit
    ---------------](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/book-your-visit)

    [
    
    Get Ready to Roar! Dinosaurs come alive these school holidays at the Jurassic Zoo.
    
    Find out more](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/jurassiczoo)
    
    [Plan Your Visit
    ---------------](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/plan-your-visit)

    [
    
    Get Ready to Roar! Dinosaurs come alive these school holidays at the Jurassic Zoo.
    
    Find out more](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/jurassiczoo)
    
    [About
    -----](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/about)

    [
    
    Get Ready to Roar! Dinosaurs come alive these school holidays at the Jurassic Zoo.
    
    Find out more](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/jurassiczoo)
    
    [Gifts
    -----](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/gifts)

* Book Your Visit
    
* Plan Your Visit
    
* About
    
* Gifts

[

Get Ready to Roar! Dinosaurs come alive these school holidays at the Jurassic Zoo.

Find out more](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/jurassiczoo)

Back

* [Book Your Visit
    ---------------](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/book-your-visit)
* [Plan Your Visit
    ---------------](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/plan-your-visit)
* [About
    -----](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/about)
* [Gifts
    -----](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/gifts)

Privacy
=======

**Updated:** October 31, 2024

### Purpose

The Australian Reptile Park is committed to ensuring all personal information is protected. We understand and appreciate that personal and confidential information that we may collect from you must be handled with respect in all aspects. This policy aims at outlining the expectation of Reptile Park staff, volunteers and Management so that any collection, use, disclosure and storage of personal information by the Reptile Park is done according to legislation and protects the privacy of all people in relation to the Reptile Park including staff, volunteers, suppliers, contractors, visitors, and others.

### Commencement of the Policy

This Policy will commence from November 11th 2021. It replaces all other policies dealing with Privacy (whether written or not).

### Application of the Policy

This Policy applies to all workplace participants of ARP including volunteers and staff

### What kind of information might the Reptile Park collect and why?

The information that the Reptile Park collects depends on the services you use or products you acquire. We may need to collect personal and sometimes sensitive information including your name, and address, email address, medical information, credit card details to name a few. Some examples of when we may collect information from you are listed below:

* Website visitors
    * statistical information including number of users,
    * who visits the Reptile Park webpage,
    * dates and times of webpage visits,
    * pages accessed,
    * users domain name,
    * precious sites visited,
    * types of browsers used,
    * users operation systems (windows or Mac);
    * We use technology called ‘cookies’ when you visit our website. Cookies are pieces of information that a website can transfer to an individual’s computer hard drive for record keeping. Your cookie may be sent at various times during your visit to our website and may be updated as you access our many different areas. The use of Cookies is an industry standard and many websites use them; they allow us to track usage patterns and compile data that help us improve our services to you! If you prefer for information not to be collected through the use of cookies, you are able to deny the cookie feature on most web browsers, or you can delete cookies from your hard drive at any time.
* Customers –
    * after purchasing items,
    * entering promotions and contests,
    * inclusions in surveys,
    * social media and online forums,
    * requested information by the Reptile Park,
    * tour and special offer participants,
    * donors and or sponsors,
    * applications for work, or voluntary work, including work experience;
* General enquiries and quoting
* Suppliers and Industry contacts

We appreciate and understand that any personal information given to the Reptile Park will only be used for the purpose agreed at the time the information is given. This may include:

* To keep our visitors informed of special promotions, offers, events and discounts. If you would prefer not to receive these updates and offers, please click ‘unsubscribe’ and you will no longer receive this information.
* To keep our visitors safe
* To identify visitors and customers
* Service development and improvement of Reptile Park processes
* For all statistical data collection online, no attempt is made to identify users, and data is used only to evaluate and improve the service provided by the Reptile Park.

Any information that we collect from you is confidential. We do not sell, lease, rent, loan, or trade the addressed stored in our databases to any unrelated third parties.

We will not disclose your personal information for purposes or to parties other that those outlined above without your consent.

### Links to other websites

The Reptile Park’s website may provide links to third party websites outside of the Reptile Park services. These linked sites are not under our control, and we are not responsible for the conduct of companies linked to our website. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website, we advise you to examine the Terms and Conditions of that website.

### Storage and security of your personal information

Any personal information that we collect about customers, including email addresses, will be kept in a secure location. The information will be accessible only by those authorised to perform normal daily tasks such as updating addresses and renewing membership. The company will take all reasonable precautions to protect the personal information it holds from any misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

The internet is not a secure environment. If you use the internet to send us any personal information, The Reptile Park will not be liable for events arising from unauthorised access to your information.

### Access to your information

You have a right to access most of the personal information we hold about you. If you wish to have access to your information, to update or complete, please send us an email or letter at the addresses provided below. If the Reptile Park does not allow you to access your personal information, we will provide you with the reasons for our decision.

The Privacy Officer

The Australian Reptile Park

PO Box 737,

Gosford NSW 2250

[\[email protected\]](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

### Opting out

You may occasionally receive promotional emails and we hope you will find these interesting and informative. If you would like to unsubscribe from receiving our mailings please click unsubscribe at the bottom of the email or contact us directly as below.

### Contact us

We take the privacy of your information seriously and it is important that you understand how we manage your personal information. If you have any questions or comments in relation to this Privacy Policy Statement please contact us by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or by mail addressed to:

Privacy Officer

the Australian Reptile Park

PO Box 737

Gosford NSW 2250

[\[email protected\]](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

You should provide us with as much detail as possible about the particular information sought, in order to help us retrieve it.

### Variations

The Australian Reptile Park Pty Ltd _reserves the right to vary, replace or terminate this policy from time to time._

Sign up to our Newsletter
-------------------------

Email \*

Name 

Gender

Please selectMaleFemaleOther

Postcode 

Sign up

We proudly acknowledge the Darkinjung people, their Country, spirit and traditions as customary owners of the lands upon which our Park stands.

###### Visitor Information

Open daily from 9am - 5pm (except Christmas Day)

###### Contact Us

[\[email protected\]](https://www.reptilepark.com.au/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

[Australian Reptile Park, Pacific Highway, Somersby, NSW, 2250](https://www.google.com/maps/place/Australian+Reptile+Park/@-33.4184085,151.2782681,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0xd66f73e70c2d211b?sa=X&ved=2ahUKEwi9lYvF3NblAhUHQY8KHX2yCwkQ_BIwF3oECAkQCA)

* * *

© Copyright 2010 - 2024 All Rights Reserved

This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms) apply.
